<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cobalt&#39;s Luna SDK Documentation on Luna SDK -- Cobalt</title>
    <link>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cobalt&#39;s Luna SDK Documentation on Luna SDK -- Cobalt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 12:56:41 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/getting-started/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/getting-started/installation/</guid>
      <description>Instructions for installing the SDK are language-specific.
Go The Go SDK supports go modules. We recommend using Go 1.11 or later. You can download the sdk using:
go get -u github.com/cobaltspeech/sdk-luna/grpc/go-luna
Alternatively, if you just import github.com/cobaltspeech/sdk-luna/grpc/go-luna in your application and run go mod tidy, it will be fetched automatically.
Python The Python SDK supports installation via pip. We recommend Python 3.5 or later, and pip 19.0 or later. You can download the sdk using:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickstart</title>
      <link>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/getting-started/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/getting-started/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>Once you have your Luna server up and running, let&amp;rsquo;s see how we can ask it to synthesize speech for some text!
First, you need to know the address (host:port) where the server is running. This document will assume the values 127.0.0.1:2727, but be sure to change those to point to your server instance. Port 2727 is the default port that the luna server binds to.
The following code snippet queries the server for a list of available voices, and uses the first listed voice to run text to speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutually Authenticated TLS</title>
      <link>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/getting-started/mutually_authenticated_tls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/getting-started/mutually_authenticated_tls/</guid>
      <description>In our recommended default setup, TLS is enabled in the gRPC setup, and when connecting to the server, clients check the server&amp;rsquo;s SSL certificate to verify that they are talking to an authentic server. This is similar to how &amp;ldquo;https&amp;rdquo; connections work in web browsers.
It may sometimes be required that both the client and server need to authenticate with each other when establishing the connection. This is possible by configuring the luna client with a valid certificate file, which it presents to the luna server when negotiating TLS connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proto Generated Docs</title>
      <link>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/protobuf/autogen-doc-cubic-proto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/protobuf/autogen-doc-cubic-proto/</guid>
      <description>The Luna API is specified as a proto file. This section of the documentation is auto-generated from the spec. It describes the data types and functions defined in the spec. The &amp;ldquo;messages&amp;rdquo; below correspond to the data structures to be used, and the &amp;ldquo;service&amp;rdquo; contains the methods that can be called.
luna.proto Service: Luna Service that implements the Cobalt Luna Text-to-Speech API
   Method Name Request Type Response Type Description     Version VersionRequest VersionResponse Queries the Version of the Server   ListVoices ListVoicesRequest ListVoicesResponse Retrieves a list of available text-to-speech voices   Synthesize SynthesizeRequest SynthesizeResponse Performs synchronous text-to-speech generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/_header/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cobaltspeech.github.io/sdk-luna/_header/</guid>
      <description>Luna SDK &amp;ndash; Cobalt</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>